&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，欢迎回来。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, welcome back from that.
我相信你找到了
I trust that you found that
在处理各种角落案件方面具有令人满意的挑战性。
satisfyingly challenging to deal with the various corner cases.
因此，让我们深入研究并尝试编写findAll实用程序。
So let's dive in and try to write a findAll utility.
公平的警告，我肯定会考虑我自己的解决方案，因为我
And fair warning, I'm definitely gonna have to look at my own solution cuz I'm
当然，我会错过这些案子中的一个，摸索着。
sure I'm gonna miss one of these cases and fumble around with.
好的，所以findAll的签名是我们想要接受一个值，
All right, so the signature of findAll is that we wanna take in a value,
我把它叫做v，我们想要得到一个列表，我把它叫做arr。
I'll call it v, and we wanna take in a list, I'll call it arr.
实际上，让我们称它为不是v，让我们称它为match，
And actually let's call that not v, let's call it match,
这就是我们要匹配的东西，arr是要从中提取的值的列表。
that's the thing we're matching against, arr is the list of values to pull from.
我们应该返回一个数组。
We're supposed to return back an array.
因此，我们将从一个空数组开始并返回该数组。
So we'll start out with an empty array and return that.
然后我们需要遍历arr中的所有值。
And then we need to loop through all of the values in arr.
&gt；&gt；Speaker 2：我认为您返回的是空数组。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: I think you're returning an empty array.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：对不起，谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Sorry, thank you.
我们希望返回ARR中与我们的匹配的所有值。
We want to return all of the values in arr that match our.
所以为了简单起见，我将做一个for of循环。
So I will do a for of loop just for simplicity.
我们将循环遍历arr中的所有值。
We'll loop over all the values in arr.
如果我们找到任何一个，我们将填充到这个返回数组中，然后返回它们，好的。
And if we find any, we'll stuff into this return array and then return them, okay.
所以相当直截了当的第一个测试是，
So fairly straightforwardly the first test is,
如果v和match是对方的对象。
if v and match are object.is of each other.
换句话说，它们严格地完全相同，所以这是一个相当容易的问题。
In other words, they are strictly exactly the same, so that's a pretty easy one.
如果Object.is并且我们使用Match和V。
If Object.is and we use match and v.
我们知道它们绝对是相同的价值，
We know that they are definitely the same value,
所以我们可以直接推入返回数组。
so we can just push into the return array.
对不起，v进入返回数组。
I'm sorry, v into the return array.
我们就停在这里，确保我们没有遗漏任何东西。
Let's just stop right here and make sure that we haven't missed anything.
让我们在特定的测试用例中尝试这一点。
Let's try this out in our particular test cases.
我们应该看到一些测试案例通过
And we should see a few test cases pass and
然后他们中的几个显然还是失败了。
then several of them obviously still failing.
所以让我们试试。
So let's try that.
而我拥有的这个小环境不喜欢底部的功能，
And this little environment I have doesn't like that function at the bottom,
所以我会暂时把它移到这里。
so I will move this up here just temporarily.
好的，我们运行这个。
Okay, so we run this.
你会注意到前三个仍然失败，但是接下来的两个通过了，
And you'll notice that the first three are failing still, but then the next two pass,
然后我们又通过了几次。
and then we get several more that pass.
所以我们做得很好。
So we did pretty good.
我们已经得到了几个这样的返回值。
We got several of these returning what we would expect already.
那我们换回去吧。
Let's switch back then.
下一个非常容易处理的情况是NULL和
And the next case that is pretty straightforward to handle is the null and
未定义的情况。
undefined case.
自述文件说，空值和未定义应该强制相互匹配。
The readme said that nulls and undefines should coercively match each other.
因此，如果Match强制等于NULL且
So if match is coercively equal to null and
V强制等于NULL，
v is coercively equal to null,
然后我们知道我们可以继续推进这一点。
then we know we can go ahead and push that.
我想我应该在这里再做一次。
I guess I should have done an else in here.
我们知道我们可以继续前进，并将其推送到阵列中。
We know we can go ahead and push that into the array.
记住匹配，对不起，空的和未定义的，
Remember the match, I'm sorry, the null and undefined,
在强制平等的情况下。
in the case of coercive equality here.
记住那是安全的，那是空的
Remember that that's safe, that nulls and
未定义者彼此强制相等，而不是其他任何东西。
undefineds are coercively equal to each other and to nothing else.
所以我们不必担心任何奇怪的负零或
So we don't have to worry about any weird corner cases of negative zeros or
在这个特殊的情况下，任何类似的事情，好吧。
anything like that in this particular case, all right.
所以如果我们要跑步，我会把那个拉到我的跑步环境里，
So if we were to run, I'll pull just that one over into my run environment here,
我们现在应该看到更多的测试通过了。
and we should see a few more of our tests now pass.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：下面有几个我认为现在
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And there is a couple down here that I think now
现在已经过去了，好吧。
that are now passing, okay.
所以进展。
So progress.
现在我们知道的下一个是我们希望允许与布尔值严格匹配，
Now the next one we know is that we wanna allow strict matching with Booleans,
意思是布尔值只匹配自己，他们根本不允许任何强制。
meaning Booleans only match themselves, they don't allow any coercion at all.
所以如果这种类型，在这种情况下，我们想要
So if the type of, and in this case we wanna
具体地说，将我们的范围缩小到Match正在发生的事情。
specifically narrow ourselves to what's happening with match.
如果匹配是布尔值，则信号
If match is a Boolean then that signals
对我们来说，我们需要严格匹配V。
to us that we need to strictly match with the v.
所以基本上在这里，如果匹配类型等于布尔值，
So basically here if type of match equals a Boolean,
并且v的类型等于布尔值，
and the type of v equals a Boolean,
因为如果没有，那么他们根本就不应该匹配。
cuz if it doesn't then they shouldn't match at all.
如果匹配的类型是Boolean，而v的类型也是Boolean，则我们知道我们有
If the type of match is Boolean and the type of v is also Boolean, we know we have
都是布尔值，但我们确实需要它们实际上是相同的布尔值。
both Booleans, but we definitely need them to actually be the same Boolean.
所以TRUE需要是TRUE，FALSE需要是FALSE。
So true needs to be true, and false needs to be false.
所以我们可以，稍后我会解释为什么要这么做，但是
So we could, and I'll explain a little bit later why we're doing this, but
我要在这里嵌套一条if语句。
I'm gonna nest an if statement in here.
在我们这些知道这两个都是布尔值的人的情况下，
In the case of those of us knowing that both of those are Booleans,
我们仍然需要检查它们是否是同一个。
we still need to check to see if they are the same one.
所以我们可以说如果匹配等于v。
So we can say if match equals v.
现在我们不需要三等号，因为我们已经限制了
Now we don't need a triple equals here because we've already restricted
表面积要知道，这两个绝对是布尔值。
the surface area to know that both of these are definitely Booleans.
我之前说过，当有布尔值时，你要避免双等号。
Now I said earlier, you wanna avoid the double equals when there's a Boolean.
这通常是正确的，但是
That's generally true, but
如果这两个都是布尔值，如果你想测试布尔值，
if both of these are Booleans, if you're trying to test against Booleans,
然后我们知道这里的双等号和三等号做的是一样的事情。
then we know that double equals here is gonna do the same thing as triple equals.
所以不管是哪种方式，你都想在那里使用双等号或三等号。
So either way, you want to use the double equals or a triple equals there.
既然类型匹配了，他们就会做完全一样的事情，好吧。
Since the types are matched, they're gonna do exactly the same thing, okay.
所以如果它们的值完全相同，
So if they are exactly the same value,
然后我们继续推向v，好的。
then we go ahead and push into v, okay.
现在，接下来的两种情况会带来更多的复杂性。
Now the next two cases where some more of the complexity comes in.
起初看起来很容易，然后我们必须记住负零的枪击
At first it seems easy and then we have to remember negative zero kind of gunks up
所有的作品都是因为它的存在方式。
all the works because of the way that it lies.
好的，首先我们说如果，让我指出，我忘记指出，我们的
Okay, so first off we said if, and let me just point out, I forgot to point out, our
object.已经在为我们处理这一部分，因此该子句已经被处理了。
object.is is already handling this part for us, so that clause is already handled.
所以现在我们所需要的就是强迫数字的字符串和
So now all we need is the strings coercing to numbers and
数字强迫成字符串。
numbers coercing to strings.
但我们需要删除那些我们不想允许发生的角落情况。
But we need to remove those corner cases that we don't want to allow to occur.
所以如果我们想要允许字符串，那么匹配可能是
So if we wanna allow strings, so a match could be
字符串，只要它不是空字符串或只有空格的字符串。
a string as long as it isn't an empty string or a white space only string.
所以让我们把它编码起来。
So let's code that up.
我们有一个else if(typeof match=“String”
We have an else if (typeof match == "string"
&amp；&amp；match.trim()！)不等于空字符串。
&amp;&amp; match.trim() !) Is not equal to the empty string.
它同时处理空字符串和任何仅空白字符串。
That handles both the empty string and any white space only strings.
因此我们知道匹配非空白，非空字符串。
So we know matches a non white space, non empty string.
我们想在这里允许强制，但是
And we wanna allow a coercion here but
只有当v是一个数字时，我们才需要那个子句。
only if v is a number, so we need that clause.
而v的类型是一个数字。
And type of v is a number.
但这并不能完全满足我们的条件，因为你会
But this won't fully satisfy our condition, because you'll
请记住，这个代码只在if else if子句逻辑方面捕获它。
remember that this one only catches it in terms of the if else if clause logic.
这个只抓住它，有点像负零，
This one only catches it, something like a negative zero,
如果它们都是负零。
if both of them are negative zero.
如果其中只有一个是负零怎么办？
What if only one of them is negative zero?
因此负零可能在匹配或v位置结束。
So a negative zero might end up in either the match or in the v position.
关于负零的强制作用，我们知道些什么，
And what do we know about the coercion that happens with a negative zero,
当我们从一个数字变成一个字符串时，我们失去了负数。
is that when we're going from a number to a string, we lose the negative.
所以我们最终会丢失，如果我们传入一个负零来匹配和
So we're gonna end up missing, if we pass in a negative zero to match against and
如果我们把它逼成一根绳子，我们最终会错过它的。
we coerce it to a string, we're gonna end up missing it.
所以我们想从我们考虑的集合中去掉任何负的零，好的。
So we want to remove from the set of our consideration any negative zeros, okay.
所以我必须加入，让我再检查一下我自己，我会
So I'm gonna have to add in, let me just double check myself here, I'm gonna have
添加一个检查，以确保我们处理的不是负零的v。
to add in a check to make sure we're not dealing with a v of negative zero.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，然后我们要做的是允许双等于
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, and then what we wanna do then is allow the double equals
强制操作告诉我们，这些都是强制平等的。
coercion operation to tell us that these are coercively equal.
所以我们已经排除了所有我们不关心的角落案件
So we've eliminated all the corner cases that we don't care about with that
围绕着if语句，现在我们只想允许
surrounding if statement, and now we just simply wanna allow
double等于要么将其放入数组，要么不将其放入数组。
the double equals to either put it in the array or not put it in the array.
和我们之前做的一样。
Same as we did before.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，如果匹配，那么最后一个子句就是相反的方式
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, and then the final clause is the other way around, if match
是一个数字，有几个数字是我们不想允许的。
is a number and there's a several numbers that we don't want to allow in there.
所以我们必须说它是不是一个数字，但它不是这些数字中的一个。
So we're gonna have to say if it's a number but it's not one of these numbers.
然后我们希望允许从字符串到数字的强制。
Then we want to allow that coercion from string to number.
好的，所以如果typeof match=“number”，那么让我们刷新一下。
All right, so if typeof match == "Number", and then let's just refresh.
我们不想在那里关注的价值观是什么？
What are the values that we didn't want to pay attention to there?
它们是NaN和两个无穷大。
They are NaN and the two infinities.
所以我要写这个
So I'm gonna write this,
实际上我会继续
actually I'll go ahead and
把它分成不同的线，
break this onto different lines here,
对你来说更具可读性。
a little more readable for you.
好的，所以我们不想考虑任何匹配是南的情况，
All right, so we don't wanna consider any case where match is NaN,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：或者它是无穷大或者
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Or it's infinity or
是阴性的
it's negative
无限好吧。
infinity, okay.
所以这三个案子肯定是出局了。
So those three cases for sure are out.
但我们会结束的，顺便说一句，我们想把条款放在里面，
But we're gonna end up, and by the way, we want the clause in there,
v的类型必须是字符串。
type of v has gotta be string.
所以我们找到了匹配的数字，而且
So we've got a match of number, and
我们希望仅当v的类型是字符串时才允许它。
we wanna allow it only if type of v is string.
但我们遇到的问题和上一个问题完全一样，
But we have the exact same problem here as we had in the previous one,
也就是说，负零可能会进来，把这里的工作搞得一团糟。
which is that negative zero could come in and gunk up the works here.
所以我们需要在这里做最后的陈述
So we need one final statement in here that
说，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那
says, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That
匹配非负零。
matches not negative zero.
所以我会把那个加进去。
So I'll add that one in.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后我们不想，记住字符串匹配，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then we don't want to, remember the string matching,
还记得这里的这些规则吗，字符串匹配？
remember these rules up here, the string matching?
所以我们不只需要知道v类型是字符串，但是
So we don't just have to know that type of v is a string, but
我们还必须知道它是一个非空的，非纯空白的字符串。
we also have to know it's a non empty, non white space only string.
所以我们也必须加入这些条款。
So we've got to add those clauses in as well.
很明显，在某些情况下，您可以进行很多重构，
And there's a lot of refactoring obviously that you can do at some point,
看到这里所有的重复。
seeing all of the duplication here.
我只是想告诉你我想要的这些角落箱子的逻辑
I'm just trying to show you the logic of what are these corner cases that I want
是为了躲避。
to be avoiding.
所以我们想说，v.trim不等于空字符串。
So we wanna say, v.trim is not equal to empty string.
这让我们进入了一个我们可以信任的场景
That gets us into a scenario where we can trust
双等于做强制性比较。
the double equals to make the coercive comparison.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：如果我没有做任何其他的遗漏，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And if I didn’t make any other omissions,
让我再检查一遍。
let me just double check.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：应该是这样。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That should be it.
所以如果我没有犯任何其他错误或者
So if I haven’t made any other mistakes or
遗漏，希望它现在可以通过我们所有的测试用例。
omissions, hopefully this should pass all our test cases now.
就像天气预报员一样，我们会祈祷希望。
Just like the weather man, we'll cross our fingers and hope.
好的，我会去找你
All right, so I'll drop in the find
所有实用程序，我们将运行它。
all utility, and we will run it.
我们都是真的，耶。
And we get all trues, yay.
好的，作为一种现实的检查。
All right, so just as a little bit of a kind of reality check here.
这是一个非常巧妙的场景，我们说，
This was a very contrived scenario where we said,
我们想实现我们自己的子集，如果你愿意的话，强制匹配。
we wanna implement our own subset, if you will, of coercive matching.
这不太可能是你要实施的东西。
That's not likely something that you're gonna implement.
但这个练习的目的是要说明更大的一点，那就是
But the purpose of this exercise was to illustrate the larger point which is
当你消除了拐角处的情况时，胁迫是安全的，
coercion can be safe when you have eliminated the corner cases,
并明确表示角落案件已被消除。
and made it obvious that the corner cases are eliminated.
所以我在这里使用的编码风格是有意的，
So the style of coding that I was using here was intentional,
也就是说，这个外部if语句消除了拐角情况。
which was to say this outer if statement is eliminating the corner cases.
然后在它里面你可以清楚地看到一个我们可以信任的双等号，那就是
And then inside it you can clearly see a double equals that we can trust that is
安全是因为那些角落的案子已经被消除了，好吧。
safe because those corner cases have been eliminated, okay.
所以这是一种关于尝试更多的更大的观点的例证
So that's kind of an illustration of the larger point about trying to be more
显然是你的类型，而不是总是试图尽可能聪明和
obvious with your types instead of always trying to be as clever as possible and
尽可能减少代码。
have the most reduced code possible.
有时一些重复和一些明显的和一点
Sometimes a bit of duplication and a bit of explicitness and a bit of
显而易见会使代码的交流更加清晰，好吧。
obviousness makes the code communicate a little bit more clearly, okay.
那么，对于强制平等的行使有什么问题吗？
So any questions about the exercise on coercive equality?
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：你能用过滤器做同样的事情吗？
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Do you have been able to do the same thing with using a filter?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以你是在问我们是否可以-
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So you're asking if we could have done-
&gt；&gt；扬声器3：不是推东西，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Instead of pushing things,
我们可以从一个开始，从数组开始，然后过滤吗？
could we start out with one, start out with the array and then filter?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，那么，我们可以有吗，你想问的是，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, so, could we have, what you're asking is,
我们是否可以实现findAll函数的匹配逻辑
could we have implemented the matching logic of the findAll function
而不是一个独立的实用程序，
instead of a utility that's standalone,
因为我们把它实现为所谓的谓词函数。
cuz we have implemented it as what's called a predicate function.
这意味着它只返回TRUE或FALSE，如果应该抛入或
Meaning it just returns true or false if something should be thrown in or
不，绝对不是，是的。
not, absolutely, yep.
所以基本上所有这些东西都是
So basically all of this stuff would be
我们的谓词函数的实质，而不是具有findAll实用程序，
the substance of our predicate function, and rather than having a findAll utility,
我们只需简单地说values.filter，然后传入我们的谓词函数。
we'd just simply say values.filter then pass in our predicate function.
所以我也是一个完全有效的方法。
So I would have been a totally valid way of doing it as well.